<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Chao's garden</title><link>https://example.org/</link><description>Chao Sun's garden. It is inspired by digital garden concept, and the most importance philosphy is 'don't have to be perfect'. With this spirit, each posts here can be imperfect or incompelete, and hopeful it grows up and develops as time goes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>csun01io@outlook.coms (Chao)</managingEditor><webMaster>csun01io@outlook.coms (Chao)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 21:47:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>tp-posts</title><link>https://example.org/posts/string-split-in-c++/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 21:47:56 +0000</pubDate><author>Chao</author><guid>https://example.org/posts/string-split-in-c++/</guid><description>C++ has no built-in string split function. This post demostrate routines like python str.split()</description></item><item><title>Preface</title><link>https://example.org/posts/preface/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 14:31:33 +0000</pubDate><author>Chao</author><guid>https://example.org/posts/preface/</guid><description>My motives for writing.
As the first post on my new site, it should tell something about my motives for writing.
Why do I write? Output as a way to learn. Inspired by Feynman&amp;rsquo;s techniques, I explain complex concepts or knowledge in simple words if I need to understand something deeply. As a programmer, I must learn, which I would love to do continuously. But I also care about how to learn fast and efficiently.</description></item><item><title>A checklist for perfectionist and procrastinate</title><link>https://example.org/posts/a-checklist-for-perfectionist-and-procrastinate/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 11:47:46 +0000</pubDate><author>Chao</author><guid>https://example.org/posts/a-checklist-for-perfectionist-and-procrastinate/</guid><description>Though there are so many factors causing my procrastination, perfectionism is one of the primary reasons I find it difficult to start doing it.
We have so many decisions to make during the day; perfectionism makes me hesitate and consumes energy in my brain. Therefore, I have this pre-programming procedure to make my life easier and try to spend more time doing actual work.
Principle Less is more time values most Do not let perfectionism stop you from achieving.</description></item></channel></rss>