<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Chao's garden</title><link>https://example.org/</link><description>Chao Sun's garden. It is inspired by digital garden concept, and the most importance philosphy is 'don't have to be perfect'. With this spirit, each posts here can be imperfect or incompelete, and hopeful it grows up and develops as time goes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>csun01io@outlook.coms (Chao)</managingEditor><webMaster>csun01io@outlook.coms (Chao)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 14:31:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Build docker image and run docker container on MacOS M1</title><link>https://example.org/posts/build-docker-image-and-run-docker-container-on-macos-m1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 14:31:33 +0000</pubDate><author>Chao</author><guid>https://example.org/posts/build-docker-image-and-run-docker-container-on-macos-m1/</guid><description>Build docker image for macOS M1 docker buildx build --platform linux/arm64 --load -t rcore_lab . Explanation docker buildx build: This initiates the Docker Buildx build process. Docker Buildx is a CLI plugin that extends the functionality of Docker&amp;rsquo;s build command, allowing for advanced features like multi-platform builds, cache import/export, and more.
--platform linux/arm64: This flag specifies the target platform for the build. In this case, it is set to linux/arm64, which means the Docker image will be built for the ARM64 architecture on a Linux operating system.</description></item><item><title>How evil a comma could be in Python</title><link>https://example.org/posts/how-evil-a-comma-could-be-in-python/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 21:58:34 +0000</pubDate><author>Chao</author><guid>https://example.org/posts/how-evil-a-comma-could-be-in-python/</guid><description>How bad a comma could be in Python?
Though I have been using Python for a couple of years, mainly as a utility to help develop software, I am still surprised by Python from time to time. Sometimes is the Sytanx sugar making me realise how elegant a Python code could be, sometimes is the caveat annoying me.
Here is the story,
in the beginning, I had a code like the one below (for the demo purpose, I simplify the code here):</description></item><item><title>String split in C++</title><link>https://example.org/posts/string-split-in-c++/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 21:47:56 +0000</pubDate><author>Chao</author><guid>https://example.org/posts/string-split-in-c++/</guid><description>C++ has no built-in string split function. This post demostrate routines like python str.split()</description></item><item><title>Preface</title><link>https://example.org/posts/preface/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 14:31:33 +0000</pubDate><author>Chao</author><guid>https://example.org/posts/preface/</guid><description>My motives for writing.
As the first post on my new site, it should tell something about my motives for writing.
Why do I write? Output as a way to learn. Inspired by Feynman&amp;rsquo;s techniques, I explain complex concepts or knowledge in simple words if I need to understand something deeply. As a programmer, I must learn, which I would love to do continuously. But I also care about how to learn fast and efficiently.</description></item><item><title>A Checklist for a perfectionist and procrastinate</title><link>https://example.org/posts/a-checklist-for-a-perfectionist-and-procrastinate/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 11:47:46 +0000</pubDate><author>Chao</author><guid>https://example.org/posts/a-checklist-for-a-perfectionist-and-procrastinate/</guid><description>Though there are so many factors causing my procrastination, perfectionism is one of the primary reasons I find it difficult to start doing it.
We have so many decisions to make during the day; perfectionism makes me hesitate and consumes energy in my brain. Therefore, I have this pre-programming procedure to make my life easier and try to spend more time doing actual work.
Principle Less is more time values most Do not let perfectionism stop you from achieving.</description></item></channel></rss>